gulfjobsbank.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy for www

**Privacy Policy for [ www.gulfjobsbank.com](http://www.gulfjobsbank.com/) **

The privacy of our visitors to [ www.gulfjobsbank.com](http://www.gulfjobsbank.com/) is important to us.

At [ www.gulfjobsbank.com](http://www.gulfjobsbank.com/), we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit [ www.gulfjobsbank.com](http://www.gulfjobsbank.com/), and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**As a career site,** [www.gulfjobsbank.com](http://www.gulfjobsbank.com/)  will ask jobseekers and employers to submit any information relevant to the job/candidate search in order to conduct/optimize the search functionality. All information is submitted exclusively on a voluntary basis. Please find below details of our member privacy practices.  
Registration

To fully participate in our job and candidate databases or search activities, we require you to register as a GULFJOBSBANK member. Non-registered users are granted partial participation access eg. non-registered jobseekers may view positions but not company contact information.

To register, we will ask for contact information (jobseekers and employers) and information on your company (employers). GULFJOBSBANK is the sole owner of information collected on the registration pages and we will not disclose this information to anyone outside of GULFJOBSBANK. Your contact information (such as name and email address may however be used to contact you about any features/services on our site which we believe may be of interest. Our goal is to provide our users with a personalized experience every time they log onto GULFJOBSBANK and to that end we may direct you to jobs/articles/forums etc. that we think may assist you in your career/lifestyle engineering activities.

**Resumes**

Members can feed their CVs in CV Builder Form thru the GULFJOBSBANK.COM and the ACTIVE mode may be specified. This would enable any employer members who is registered with our service to access your CV. We are not responsible for the privacy of any copies of your CV that are subsequently retained by employer members in their own private files and databases. 

As an additional privacy function, jobseekers have the option to block the name of their current employer from any employer searches. This function is easily available on our CV Builder. Your CV will therefore appear in candidate searches with your latest experience record but without details of your current employer. This is a critical feature as the last person you would like viewing your CV is your current employer.  
You may edit/change information on your CV at any point in time. You may also remove your CVs from our databases at any point in time.

**Job Postings**

Employers are asked to submit detailed contact information and information about the position requirements as part of their job posting activity. Information is submitted purely voluntarily. Job details may be viewed by any registered jobseeker members. Non-members may view position but do not have access to contact details; they must register first to be able to contact your company. As an additional privacy feature, employers may hide their company name when their jobs are viewed online. Your privacy will thus be assured while jobseekers have the option to reply to the posting.  
You may change/modify/delete any information you provide at any point in time.  
Your Workspace

Registered jobseekers and employers have access to a personal workspace from where they can manage/document their job/candidate search history. All information in this space can only be viewed by the registered user(s) and accessed after logging in with your password.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on [ www.gulfjobsbank.com](http://www.gulfjobsbank.com/) to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)  

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Privacy Commitment Changed**

GULFJOBSBANK will continue to commit itself to protecting and maximizing our users' privacy. We will update you on an ongoing basis on any changes/enhancements in our privacy practices

 Updated On 25.05.2009
